Connor Guard

Brisbane, QLD / 0406304199 / Connor.guard@gmail.com

Software developer undergraduate, studying at Queensland University of Technology. Experienced customer service representative with strong IT knowledge. Able to apply customer service concepts to IT, improving user experience for clients, employees, and administration. A skilled leader and thrives in team environments.

Experience

Electrical Trade Assistant @ SFR Electrical

Kedron, QLD // Nov 2020 - Present

Part of a small and collaborative team, assisting qualified electricians with the installation of PV Solar Systems and batteries across Brisbane, QLD. Predominantly on residential buildings.

Data Processing Officer @ HAWCS

Northlakes, QLD // May 2020 - Nov 2020

Provided effective and efficient data processing by snapping and manipulating GIS Data. Assisted with quality control and preparation of GIS layers. Developed problem solving and computer skills.

Food and Beverage Attendant @ Event Cinemas (Gold Class)

Northlakes, QLD // Nov 2019 - Feb 2020

Responsible for handling reservations, greeting customers, taking orders, serving food and drink, cleaning tables, and washing up. Developed skills working under pressure and teamwork.

Lifeguard @ Everyone Active

Birmingham, UK // Jan 2019 - Aug 2019

My role was to maintain swimmer safety, monitor water conditions and guest behaviour while enforcing safety rules. Developed skills in negotiation and conflict resolution.

Internship – IT Support Technician @ Shell Energy Retail Limited

Coventry, UK // Jan 2017 - Jan 2018

Supported employees who are experiencing issues with computers and software. Provided Support in person, over the phone & online. Addressed issues ranging from network systems to individual desktop computers.

Summer Internship – Front-End Developer @ Access to Music

Birmingham, UK // 2016

Web UX / UI designer, optimizing web pages for maximum efficiency, and maintaining brand consistency across all web pages, among other duties.

Education

Queensland University of Technology

Bachelor of Information Technology, Graduating 2023

- Majoring in Computer Science
- Current GPA 6.29

GCE Advanced Level

Mathematics, computer science, media studies

Skills

Programming Languages

 ${\it C\#,\,C,\,Python,\,Java,\,SQL,\,HTML5,\,CSS,\,JavaScript}$

Libraries & Frameworks

React, Node.js, Chart.js, Bootstrap

Design

Microsoft suite applications, Adobe applications, InVision, Webflow

Soft skills

Customer service, leadership, desire to learn, problem solving.

Certificates

RSA, Responsible Service of Alcohol Certificate NPLQ, National Pool Lifeguard Qualification First Aid & Defibrillator Certificate

Projects

Ordinal - asset trading platform

Java desktop application that distributes company assets within a business through a marketplace system.

International Happiness Report

A React web application that analyzes the annual international happiness report data.

Interests

Reading, traveling, running